<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>SupaSidebar Updates</title>
        <item>
            <title>Version 0.12.0</title>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:41:00 +0530</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>18</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>0.12.0</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <description><![CDATA[
<h1 id="supasidebar-0.12.0">SupaSidebar 0.12.0</h1>
<h2 id="whats-new">What’s New</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Dock Mode</strong>: Sidebar now pushes browser windows aside instead of overlapping them. Windows automatically return to full width when sidebar hides. This mimics the behaviour of inbuilt sidebar in any browser.</li>
<li><strong>Smart Folders for Files</strong>: Smart folders can now automatically organize files and folders (not just links) based on conditions like file type, path, or name patterns.</li>
<li><strong>Save All Tabs to Folder</strong>: Quickly save all currently open tabs to a folder with a single action.</li>
<li><strong>Custom Pin Icons</strong>: Added ability to manually set custom icons for pinned sites.</li>
<li><strong>Compact Sidebar View</strong>: New sidebar view option that shows only favicons, taking up minimal space.</li>
<li><strong>Smart Folder Operations</strong>: Smart folders now support the same operations as normal folders, including moving to different spaces.</li>
<li><strong>Improved Tab Distinction</strong>: Better visual contrast for tabs from different browser windows.</li>
<li><strong>Favicons in Live Tabs</strong>: Live tabs now show favicons</li>
<li><strong>Toolip</strong>: Tooltip on hover to get full link and info about link or folder.</li>
<li><strong>Swipe to Change Space</strong>: Swipe left or right with 2 fingers to move between spaces.</li>
<li><strong>Peek View</strong>: Cmd + Click to preview link in a mini window.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="bug-fixes">Bug Fixes</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fixed issue where clicking the cloud status menu icon would trigger hide on deactivate behavior, causing the sidebar to hide unexpectedly.</li>
<li>Fixed critical bug where save shortcut was not working in Arc and Dia browsers.</li>
<li>Fixed issue where users were stuck on the onboarding screen.</li>
<li>Fixed bug where smart folders and regular folders were not shown until there was at least one link in the space.</li>
</ul>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure
                url="https://github.com/auspy/supasidebar-updates/releases/download/v0.12.0/supasidebar_v0.12.0.zip"
                sparkle:edSignature="6tJQxaSHdbc/tnoZCfwuKJh+tP1TPLwNif/tiLhCZMYUcz4+9GfRxCgjsFRmAPyGu979NSY7N9vsASwp7GUjAw=="
                length="6560763"
                type="application/octet-stream"/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
