<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>SupaSidebar Updates</title>
        <item>
            <title>Version 0.15.0</title>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:18:00 +0530</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>21</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>0.15.0</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <description><![CDATA[
<h1 id="supasidebar-0.15.0">SupaSidebar 0.15.0</h1>
<h2 id="whats-new">What’s New</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Air Traffic Control</strong>: Create rules to automatically route links to specific spaces based on URL patterns. Filter by source browser and choose whether rules apply when saving or opening links.</li>
<li><strong>Profile &amp; Browser-Linked Spaces</strong>: Link any space to a browser profile or a specific browser. Switching spaces instantly raises the correct window using Accessibility APIs. Includes profile discovery across Safari, Chrome, Firefox, Edge, and Arc.</li>
<li><strong>Smart Attach</strong>: Sidebar now truly integrates with your browser. It auto-shows when your browser is in focus, brings the browser forward when activated, and hides when you switch to other apps. Choose between Independent and Smart Attach modes.</li>
<li><strong>Auto-Tiling</strong>: Browser windows automatically arrange alongside the sidebar. Smart mode tiles only the active profile’s windows, while All mode tiles every browser window.</li>
<li><strong>Shared Spaces</strong>: Publish any space as a shareable link collection. Others can view and import your shared spaces into their own sidebar.</li>
<li><strong>Import &amp; Export</strong>: Back up and transfer your data with the new .ssb file format. Export everything or import from another device.</li>
<li><strong>Spotlight-Like Search</strong>: Completely redesigned search with token matching, inline autocomplete, and selection memory. Finds links by title, URL, notes, and tags.</li>
<li><strong>Expanded Pin Icons</strong>: Customize pinned link icons with emoji, SF Symbols, or upload your own image.</li>
<li><strong>Drag-to-Reorder Pinned Tabs</strong>: Rearrange your pinned links directly by dragging them into the order you want.</li>
<li><strong>Copy All URLs</strong>: Bulk copy or open all URLs from any folder, smart folder, or live tabs. Also works with multi-selected links.</li>
<li><strong>Paste from Clipboard</strong>: Right-click any folder or space to paste a URL directly from your clipboard.</li>
<li><strong>Tab Restore on Space Switch</strong>: When switching between profile spaces, a prompt shows any tabs that were open before with options to restore or skip. Configurable per-space with a “Don’t ask again” option.</li>
<li><strong>Fill Screen Shortcut</strong>: Press Cmd+Opt+F to toggle fill screen mode, instantly positioning the sidebar and browser to use your full display.</li>
<li><strong>Adaptive Spaces Bar</strong>: Arc-style bottom bar that dynamically sizes space icons based on available width - icons shrink progressively as you add more spaces, with dock-style hover magnification.</li>
<li><strong>More AI Models</strong>: Added Ollama as an AI tagging provider alongside the expanded MLX model list for on-device tag suggestions.</li>
<li><strong>Space Switch Suggestion</strong>: When you activate a browser or profile linked to a different space, the sidebar suggests switching to the matching space automatically.</li>
<li><strong>Free Tier Update</strong>: The free plan now includes 3 spaces instead of 1, giving new users more room to organize before upgrading.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="improvements">Improvements</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Don’t Reload Open Tabs</strong>: Clicking a saved or pinned link that’s already open now switches to it without reloading the page.</li>
<li><strong>Edit from Context Menu</strong>: Pinned links context menu now includes Edit and Open Preview options.</li>
<li><strong>Preferred Browser</strong>: “Browser Saved From” renamed to “Preferred Browser” for clarity across the app and menu bar.</li>
<li><strong>Auto-Raise Browser</strong>: Opening the sidebar now automatically brings the browser window to the front, so it’s always ready alongside your tabs. With Smart Attach enabled, the sidebar and browser automatically tile side-by-side or fill the screen together.</li>
<li><strong>Floating Tooltips</strong>: Space icons now show floating tooltips on hover for better identification.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="bug-fixes">Bug Fixes</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fixed folder count not updating correctly after pinning a link.</li>
<li>Fixed multi-select drag not moving all selected links together.</li>
<li>Fixed subfolder spacing gap and header height shifting on hover.</li>
<li>Fixed crash when scrolling through folders with 80+ tabs.</li>
<li>Fixed live tabs causing lag with 30+ open tabs.</li>
<li>Fixed sidebar not staying within screen bounds in attach mode.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="performance">Performance</h2>
<ul>
<li>Optimized folder tree rendering for large collections (80+ tabs per folder).</li>
<li>Adaptive live tabs polling - faster when active, slower when sidebar is hidden.</li>
</ul>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure
                url="https://github.com/auspy/supasidebar-updates/releases/download/v0.15.0/supasidebar_v0.15.0.zip"
                sparkle:edSignature="W20gK7F/Hs+sU1T9738NgHWTgFsr+c4AjdC8Wx3SYTdeaK06lOmgSvs+i8hoIm30018NkaqoZRFyT9MVftlWAQ=="
                length="18223709"
                type="application/octet-stream"/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
